

Dorian-Ioan VELICI

Date of birth: 15/12/1996

Place of birth: Lugoj, Romania

Nationality: Romanian

Gender: Male

CONTACT

Spl. 1 Decembrie 1918, bl. 29, ap.

305500 Lugoj, Romania (Home)



(+40) 720390573

https://dorian-ioan-velici.github.io/ personal-website/index.html

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/dorian-ioan-velici/

+40 720 390 573 **(WhatsApp)**



ABOUT ME

I am a problem-solving person. Both in my personal & professional space, I particularly enjoy using my skills to solve challenging problems, to future improve processes and to prevent less desired outcomes from occurring.

By working at FORVIA Hella Lugoj as a Technical Assistant in the Backend Area, I gained on-field demonstrated experience, developed my general knowledge and analytical skills around PCB-testing equipment, CNC routing machines & automatic soldering stations by configuring / maintaining the equipment, optimizing / redesigning the programs and, finally - improving the overall manufacturing processes when needed.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lugoj, Romania

Website Developer

11/10/2024 - Current

Website development - both programming & designing web pages in my spare time.

FORVIA Hella Lugoj, Romania

Business or Sector Manufacturing | **Department** PCBA Production (Backend Area) | **Email** dorianioan.velici@forvia.com | **Website** https://www.hella.com/hella-ro/

Technical Assistant (Backend Area)

27/04/2023 - Current

My usual tasks consist in:

- regular analytical, troubleshooting & problem-solving activities;
- technical maintenance, equipment configuration & repair;
- program optimization / redesign for many essential devices used at PCB-manufacturing processes;
- enhance the overall production conditions by assuring regular quality control & efficiency of machinery and operators;
- maintain accurate records of production processes, procedures and technical information;
- continuous process workflow improvement.

The equipment I'm most familiar with:

- ICT / EOL test stands (such as Aeroflex 4250 & National Instruments NI LabVIEW) and Takaya Flying Probe Tester;
- automatic selective soldering machines (SEHO SelectLine C systems);
- CNC routing machines used in the PCB depaneling process (Schunk & Asys Divisio 2000 Ergo millings);
- Maestro 4S cutting stations;
- plus other PCB-manufacturing factory equipment.

Lugoj, Romania

IT Technician

02/06/2015 - Current

In my spare time I also:

- Configure, upgrade & optimize Windows OS-based systems;
- Troubleshoot & fix hardware failures;
- Improve the overall performance, gain stability & fix problems caused by software-related issues.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/10/2017 - 01/07/2021 Timisoara, Romania

Information Technology Engineer "Ioan Slavici" University - Faculty of Engineering

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Romanian

Other language(s):

English

Listening C1

Spoken production B2

Reading C1

Spoken interaction B2

Writing C1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

SKILLS

NI LabVIEW | Computer Literacy | PCB Debugging | Process Optimization | CNC Programming | Process Failure Mode Effects Analysis | Website Development

DRIVING LICENCE



Driving Licence: AM **Driving Licence:** B